JACOB GIBSON

IT systems master student

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an IT professional motivated to improve the whole organisation's performance through better IT systems that work for day-to-day operations. I have expertise in a range of operating systems, hardware and software. The world of computing and IT systems especially thrill me. I would love to share this passion as part of your team in the future.

	m		

gibson.jacob.b@gmail.com

Mobile

07990 277383

Address

65 Ednaston Rd Nottingham NG7 2JF

SKILLS

IT Troubleshooting	g
Windows and Linux systems	
SQL Databases	
Python and Java	

LANGUAGES

English	
French	

HOBBIES

Volleyball, design, outdoors and hiking, music and concerts, reading

EDUCATION

2:1 MSc Cloud and Enterprise Computing

Nottingham Trent University

2020 - 2021

Key skills gained:

- Learning to design and manage Enterprise-level IT systems
- Overseeing the adoption of Cloud Systems for businesses
- Managing the security of computer networks and Cloud Systesm
- Integrating best IT practices into the firm's operations
- Software engineering

2:1 BA (Hons) Computing

Nottingham Trent University

2016 - 2020

Notable modules: Information Systems Management, Business Analysis, Information and Database Engineering, Information Security

Tapton Secondary School

2014 - 2016

A-level passes in three subjects: Business Studies (A), Maths (B) and English Literature (B)

Tapton Secondary School

2009 - 2014

11 GCSEs, grade A*-C including Maths and English

JACOB GIBSON

IT systems master student

WORK EXPERIENCE

	Placement	vear	in	IT	div	/is	ic	n
--	------------------	------	----	----	-----	-----	----	---

ASOS - Online fashion retailer, London ____ 2018 - 2019

- Supporting the development and launch of new iPad/iPhone customer app
- Processing tickets related to software and hardware challenges
- Identifying and resolving network issues
- Optimising website performance using SEO
- Managing website content and e-mail marketing

3-month summer IT internship

Drivy - Carsharing app provider, London ____ 2017

- Addressing employees' tech issues related to hardware and software
- Updating and maintaining virus protection software
- Configuring wide area networks (WAN) or local area networks (LAN)
- Installing new hardware and software systems or components
- Performing routine maintenance or standard repairs to networking components or equipment

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Online courses

- Google IT Automation with Python Professional Certificate (on coursera.org)
- System Administratio and IT Infrastructure Systems (on coursera.org)
- Python for Data Science (on edX.org)

Youth club volunteer

M8S Youth Club, Nottingham ___ 2017 - today

Helping children with learning disabilities and supporting them in activities such as indoor and outdoor games, cooking, reading, and on outings like hiking trips, bowling or canoeing

REFERENCES

References will be provided upon request